It has begun! Ana channel applause!
What are you doing today?
I'm hoping to have you create a one-week wardrobe
I'd like you to make a one-week coordination.
One week?
One week!
A week is a long time.
This show is a variety show where Ana will challenge herself in various ways.
It's ready.
Please tell me the theme of the show, and I'll tell you what it is.
I'm the piano itself.
That's it!
Here it is.
Please explain the point.
The point is...
I was aware of the discovery and the state rights.
Like this
Pure white, white already, esked a white dog and a black dog
Such a pure white and such a beautiful white and such a beautiful black
Such a beautiful white and such a black!
The point is that it's all black!
I used only black and white.
I wanted to use a round cuff, but there were only student blouses available, so I used a student's blouse.
I'm using a student's blouse... from the children's clothing department. It was in a strange place.
There was only one or so.
But the Kagora is cute.
It's a national right here.
And the eight rights.
Like this.
What made you think of the piano?
I wanted something dressy.
I wanted something dressy so I could go to recitals and bake sales.
Then I thought of a piano.
These are all Shimamura.
The shoes are Shimamura, too.
The shoes are 2,420 yen.
The whole outfit is 6,237 yen.
That's so cheap!
But they look cute.
Yes, they are.
Cute!
It's done!
What is the theme?
Please tell me the theme... the theme is Kotobukitaisha. I'm a Ura-red girl who likes o-hagi (rice cakes)
Please tell me the theme.
Hey!
Here it is!
I wasn't sure what the theme was, but it looks like this.
It's important to cut out the bones.
What's this? A dry-erase wedding?
"Sosai"?
I'm actually wearing a tie with the word "Sosai" on it.
But it's cute and has cranes on it.
Aren't cranes cute? I thought it was a good choice.
It's the kind of tie your uncle wears to weddings.
But I think it's cute.
I went with white.
There were black and blue ones too, but I went with white.
This one and this one were in the children's area
They didn't sell many skirts
I chose this one because it was prettier in the children's area.
The waist was a little too tight, so I added a belt.
That's 759 yen!
Cheap!
I also found this one on sale.
What do you call them? Like loose socks or leg warmers.
And an Adidas jersey.
I usually dress like this.
So it's rather natural? It's natural.
Is this the same shirt and shoes you wear to the piano?
The shirt and shoes are the same as at the piano.
Not at all. This one is more like a toy.
Cute.
That's the theme.
That's why the theme is
Koumya is Kotobuki-Taisha!
Ura-red girls who like o-hagi (rice cakes)
Do you read "I like o-hagi"?
I'm the one who likes onagi.
Don't ask me that, I'm an idiot!
The whole body is 12,746 yen.12,746 yen for the whole body.
It's done.
What's the theme?
I don't want to get involved with women.
I'm a licensed chef.
No girl stuff.
Like a boy.
Here you go, men's stuff.
This is a men's set-up for a 4L.
Dare to be big.
I think this would be cute on a girl.
I think they'd look cute with their hair tied up or in twin-tails.
I think it's cute.
It's a little scary because of the velour on the side.
Yes, it's a strange velour.
You can only find these in Nakajima Village.
This is velour.
Velour here, too.
They went to the trouble of making it velour.
That's right.
First place.
It's definitely shiny, isn't it?
It's very special. It's a coordinated look that you can only get at Shimamura.
The inside could be used with a blouse.
And this is Katabuki Taisha.
I'm getting married to the woman I just met.
I'm also wearing an engagement ring.
It's amazing. It's jarrah-jarrah-see.
Are there a lot of accessories this time?
This time I have a lot of accessories, four necklaces and three rings.
The most important one is a skateboard necklace.
Skateboard necklace skateboard?
Skateboard?
Skate necklace.
I also bought a ring and the one on his hand?
This was a three-piece set.
The rings, the set of three, 429 yen.
That's 429 yen.
This one is 429 yen.
Visual tick.
Will you marry me?
Shoes? What shoes? And these sandals.
I'm trying to be cute here.
They're on sale for less than a grand?
Yes, they are.
These are very comfortable to walk in. They look good.
I can't go to a convenience store and buy anything with it.
How far can you go?
I'm going to use it for my wedding later on.
I'm getting married to that woman.
What is the theme?
What's the theme?
I don't want any women in my life.
I'm a licensed chef.
What's a chef's license?
My future wife.
For her.
I'm going to be a chef, a pastry chef.
What's your specialty?
My specialty is bavarois.
It's not much, but it's not expensive.
That's cheap.
It looks good.
Is it done?
What's the theme?
Don't say "pajamas" again... let's make me look good.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Oh, please.
Oh!
Mwah-mwah.
Here you go.
Pajamas.
This is already Shimamura.
I buy pajamas there.
All the time.
And this time, when pajamas are available, I buy pajamas.
And this time there were pajamas, so I bought pajamas!
And this...And this.
What is that?
This is for all kinds of things.
I know that the cook was here earlier, but... to be honest, I was thinking that...
I was going to give it to the cook.
I forgot about it.
That's why I'm holding it.
It wasn't really supposed to be like this.
But it's cute.
Isn't it a little cute?
I knew I wear pajamas a lot,
I was allowed to wear pajamas for at least one day.
But this, after all, is a student's bra that I've been wearing around all my life...
What's a "jajan"?
Blouse.
Blouse?
By wearing a blouse.
At the city hall or at the office
Or an office.
I mean, you can go to the Capitol.
They're just pajamas, but I'm wearing them inside.
It looks totally different.
That's right.
That's why I said, "I'm not wearing pajamas.
I've been wearing the shirt for about four days.
It's been done for four days.
You've been wearing it the whole time.
The whole outfit costs 6,028 yen.
That's 6,000 yen.
It's done. What's the theme?
What's the theme?
Grandpa, where did you go?
1,000 yen.
I'll take care of it.
Yes, sir.
It's very casual, isn't it?
It's a little casual. Anyone can wear it.
These are children's clothes for little people.
Small size.
And the top?
The top is a costume I bought for my grandfather.
It's the kind of thing your grandfather would wear.
What's that? The dog?
I bought it because the dog was cute.
It comes in a bunch of different colors.
I picked this one.
But there were so many more variations.
This one's cute.
The shoes and socks are women's?
They're women's. They're easy to wear.
I found some nice, simple ones.
I got these at the baby place, too.
What do you put in that?
This?
Rice.
Enough rice to make one rice ball.
I'm going with the Kiyoshi Yamashita style here.
It's filled with the Kiyoshi Yamashita of 2025.
2025.
Where'd Grandpa go?
Grandpa...
Since my grandpa went away...
I'm the one who did it, but...
I'm the one who lost him.
I used to wear his clothes.
I put his clothes on, and I put his precious rice in the box...
The scariest girl's backyard.
Too scary.
So it's Grandpa's.
You mean it's all there?
What's this?
Like this.
Shimamura style.
I see what you mean.
It's a style. There was no style.
It's done.
What is the theme?
Matching with my son. He is a big fan of festivals.
I'm sure he's a nice guy, but I don't want to be around him. I'd like to be with him.
Please.
I don't like my clothes. Please.I do not like my clothes. Please.
Are you dressed for the outdoors today?
Yes, I am.
They are summer clothes.
They are my summer clothes.
I am with my son.
Are you a father?
You mean I'm a father? I am a father.
This time.
I said a week's coding.
I'm changing people.
I'm wearing the same outfit as my son.
He's a very nice guy. I'm a very nice guy.
He's a very nice man.
But he gets hurt easily.
He's the type of guy who gets a little overzealous on his skin at Fuji Rock
I'm the type of person who breaks bones and gets airsick.
That's what you mean.
Is that a women's top?
Is this a bodice?
No. What is it?
Boys?
It says 5L.
It's a manger.
It's a 5L. That's a pretty big size.
It says 5L.
The great thing about Shimamura is
It comes in a 5L size.
It's not so easy to find a 5L
You can wear it no matter how big you are
This one with a whale emblem is also available.
We have a lot of different styles, so even if you've never seen it before, you can wear it.
It's also available in a variety of colors.
I've never seen anything like it.
With the dog I just saw.
The dog and the whale.
This whale is probably the trend right now.
I'm wearing this right now.
You should buy one.
And this whale is bleeding a little bit.
I bought it because it's so cute, and it's not even 7,000 yen for the whole body.
Wow, that's cheap!
For the whole body!
The whole body.
The hat was on sale, too. So it's only 1000 yen.
Wow! It's from Atitas.
The fabric is good and the color is nice.
It's easy to use.
Posed like that by an ad?
Just so.
That's the one on the news, Shimamura. Here we go.
What's the theme?
I've had 10 children.
A housewife who doesn't give in to ridicule.
We'll be there 24 hours a day.
Please. Please do it. I'm a housewife who won't be defeated. 24 hours a day.
Please.
What do you think?
It's kind of cute.
Look.
What's that on top?
They're pajamas.
I found them in the pajamas section.
I used them as a jacket.
Oh, what? And they're cute.
Yes, it is.
They're ears.
You want to do it?
Yeah, sure.
It's a sore one, don't worry.
It's really a bear.
It's a bear, like you're in costume.
Yeah, it looks like a costume.
That's great.
And here's another bear.
What's this? Ladies.
Kids' girls' clothes.
Girl's children's clothing.
It's got a bear on it.
A bear.
I've never seen one before.I've never seen it before.
I've never seen you in a bear suit before.
I saw a dress that looked like the same color.
You got it?
Women's.
Socks for elementary school kids, I guess.
They have a cute little logo on them.
Yes, they're quite long when they're stretched.
The shoes are women's, right?
Yes, they are.
They're ladies'.
They look really cute with this outfit.
And here, this is a loaf of bread.
Bread.
This is a croissant, but the kids say "crap, crap, crap," and I feel sorry for them.
Mom bought this croissant because she thought it was cute, but the kids say "crap, crap, crap" and she's really embarrassed and doesn't want to carry it.
But we don't have a lot of money and I have to feed 10 people, so I have to put up with it and shop with this all the time.
I am a strong mother.
You go to the supermarket and buy a lot of things in that outfit, don't you?
That's right. I put bread in here.
Kraus bread, for example.
You did your hair for the first time, right?
So, when I got tired, the kids would ask me why I wore my hair in such a strange way even though I was a mom, or why I wore so many bears even though I was a mom, and I would get tortured in painful places.
I get hit in the painful places all the time. But she says she will do what she likes,
But I'm a strong-willed mother who says she will do what she likes.
The whole body is about 6,500 yen.
From head to toe, 6,500 yen.
A good deal.
I use this with my daughter and second daughter,
I use it together with my daughter and second daughter.
How did you like it?
There are a lot of clothes that I don't usually wear,
I think I did a good job, because I was able to find a bargain, or rather, I was able to make a coordinated anago that is unique to me.
I think I did my best. It's a lot of work.
So there are that many clothes.
Yes, there are so many different kinds of clothes.
They even have a 5L, and they've got that dog and whale trend under control, so...
I'll have to go.
Let's go back to the other store and hang out a bit.
Oh no, no, no.
Don't ever do a series.
Let's keep it tight. I can't.
I can't do it, I won't do it.
I can't do it!
you